<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CollegeApp Project</string>
    <string name="about">Government Residence Women Polytechnic, Tasgaon is an institute established in the 2009-2010 under DTE, Mumbai Maharashtra and is
        approved by AICTE and affiliated to MSBTE. </string>
    <string name="about_us1">Government Residence Women Polytechnic Tasgaon is one of the best leading
        polytechnic established in the Maharashtra State
        in 2009,having an aim to spread technical education in the part of rural area in order to empower
        women for making India ethically and technically strong.This institute aims to develop the eminent
        engineers who are competent and committed to the highest professional standards in the field of
        engineering and technology.O</string>
    <string name="about_us2">Our institute provides all kinds of facilities under different platforms
        to encourage and guide the students in a conductive atmosphere where all round talent of the students
        is nurtured and flourished.This institute is located in very pleasant environment, 3 km away from
        Tasgaon city,10km away from Bhilvadi railway
        station,40 km away from Miraj railway Junction on TasgaonManerajuri Road.
        The college campus is spread over 22 acres area with huge academic buildings along with a separate
        residential faculty and staff quarters, hostels zone.</string>
    <string name="civilinfo1"> The department of Civil Engineering (CE) is established
        in the year 2013-14 with a sanctioned intake of 60.
        This program offers students a sound grounding in the fundamentals of civil engineering
        and prepares them to cater the needs of industry and society.
        The three year diploma course lays out emphasis on practical work.
        The laboratories in the department are well equipped.
        Along with curriculum provided by MSBTE the various trainings, expert talks,
        workshops, industrial visits are regularly arranged by the department.</string>
    <string name="civilinfo2">
        The three year diploma course lays out emphasis on practical work.
        The laboratories in the department are well equipped.
        Along with curriculum provided by MSBTE the various trainings, expert talks,
        workshops, industrial visits are regularly arranged by the department.</string>
</resources>